<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1"?>
<!-- 50 Top Website Considerations; All rights reserved; Redweb 2009 -->
<items>
	<item>
		<title>Are you making the most of metadata?</title>
	</item>
	
	<item>
		<title>How far are you optimising your pages for search engines?</title>
	</item>
	
	<item>
		<title>How will you aggregate links in from other sites and social networks?</title>
	</item>
	
	<item>
		<title>Remember to write your content for people not search engines</title>
	</item>
	
	<item>
		<title>Don't try and trick a search engine into thinking your content is relevant, make it relevant</title>
	</item>
	
	<item>
		<title>High accessibility standards are great for search engine optimisation</title>
	</item>
	
	<item>
		<title>Invest in user testing at all stages</title>
	</item>
	
	<item>
		<title>Is your information architecture obvious, simple and scalable?</title>
	</item>
	
	<item>
		<title>Have you done research with your target audiences?</title>
	</item>
	
	<item>
		<title>Developing key personas can help you identify with your audiences</title>
	</item>
	
	<item>
		<title>Monitor your analytics regularly to improve areas where visitors may be dropping out</title>
	</item>
	
	<item>
		<title>Think about the journey and experience of the users of your site</title>
	</item>
	
	<item>
		<title>Simplicity is key to great usability</title>
	</item>
	
	<item>
		<title>Is your site scalable in the future?</title>
	</item>
	
	<item>
		<title>Are social sites and networks important to your audience?</title>
	</item>
	
	<item>
		<title>Are you building or engaging a community?</title>
	</item>
	
	<item>
		<title>What are your competitors doing well and how could they improve?</title>
	</item>
	
	<item>
		<title>How much time do you have?</title>
	</item>
	
	<item>
		<title>How much budget do you have?</title>
	</item>
	
	<item>
		<title>How will future phases of the site build on the initial success?</title>
	</item>
	
	<item>
		<title>Have you secured all the URLs and sub domains you plan on using?</title>
	</item>
	
	<item>
		<title>Do you need to support more than one language?</title>
	</item>
	
	<item>
		<title>Does your site need to be viewed on other devices such as mobile phones and internet ready consumer electronics</title>
	</item>
	
	<item>
		<title>How does your brand work online?</title>
	</item>
	
	<item>
		<title>Consistency aids usability and good user experience</title>
	</item>
	
	<item>
		<title>Can users personalise their experience?</title>
	</item>
	
	<item>
		<title>What level of accessibility are you aiming for?</title>
	</item>
	
	<item>
		<title>How can you help your users achieve their goals on your site?</title>
	</item>
	
	<item>
		<title>Design your page layouts according to the priority of your content</title>
	</item>
	
	<item>
		<title>Are all your calls to action clear and obvious?</title>
	</item>
	
	<item>
		<title>You have less than 6 seconds to grab a visitors attention if they land on your homepage from a search engine</title>
	</item>
	
	<item>
		<title>How will you migrate your existing content?</title>
	</item>
	
	<item>
		<title>How much content already exists?</title>
	</item>
	
	<item>
		<title>How can you harness user generated content?</title>
	</item>
	
	<item>
		<title>Has your content been written for online use?</title>
	</item>
	
	<item>
		<title>Can you provide your content in a more engaging and rich way?</title>
	</item>
	
	<item>
		<title>Think carefully about the tone of voice you are using</title>
	</item>
	
	<item>
		<title>Keep compliant with data security legislation</title>
	</item>
	
	<item>
		<title>Do you have any training needs before the new site is handed over?</title>
	</item>
	
	<item>
		<title>Do you have a hosting partner?</title>
	</item>
	
	<item>
		<title>How quickly can you recover your data if something goes wrong?</title>
	</item>
	
	<item>
		<title>Do you have a process for deployment and updates</title>
	</item>
	
	<item>
		<title>How will you update the site</title>
	</item>
	
	<item>
		<title>How often will you add, update and refresh content</title>
	</item>
	
	<item>
		<title>Who will add new content to your site and how will this be managed?</title>
	</item>
	
	<item>
		<title>Do you have a thorough test plan in place?</title>
	</item>
	
	<item>
		<title>How do you truly engage your users?</title>
	</item>
	
	<item>
		<title>Are you giving the user the best experience of your brand?</title>
	</item>
	
	<item>
		<title>How will you measure your success?</title>
	</item>
	
	<item>
		<title>How fast are your pages loading?</title>
	</item>
	
	<item>
		<title>How do you balance business needs with user goals?</title>
	</item>
	
	<item>
		<title>How do you capture meaningful data?</title>
	</item>
	
	<item>
		<title>Are you communicating or broadcasting?</title>
	</item>
	
	<item>
		<title>Do you have team buy in from all your key decision makers?</title>
	</item>
	
	<item>
		<title>Do you have an information or sales bias?</title>
	</item>
	
	<item>
		<title>What browsers will support your site?</title>
	</item>
	
	<item>
		<title>How will you bring users to your site?</title>
	</item>
	
	<item>
		<title>How will you get users to keep returning to your site?</title>
	</item>
</items>